convertpdftoword.org 2012-10-23

# Convert PDF to Word Free Online – Privacy Policy

Convertpdftoword.org is committed to ensuring that your privacy as a visitor of our website and as a user of our services is protected.

## Use of Personal Information

We will not share, sell, lease, disclose, transfer, transmit or rent any personal information you submit through the Convertpdftoword.org website without your consent. 

## Handling uploaded and converted files

We store uploaded files to our server only temporarily for conversion purposes. When the conversion process ends, we delete those files from our servers automatically. The converted file is stored on our servers for 24 hours so that the user can download it.

There is no back-up of stored files. Contents of the files are not being monitored in any way by Convertpdftoword.org or any other third party. The content of the file is accessible via download link users receive in their email.

## Emails addresses

We will email you only for conversion purposes: 1. to send you a converted file and 2. inform you about the status of a conversion process. Your email is never going to be rented, shared or sold to a third party. 

We will send you email updates only if you subscribe to them and double opt-in. Each message will include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from future mailings if you wish to cancel your subscription at any time.

## Cookies

Convertpdftoword.org might put a cookie on your website. A website cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be deleted from your browser. You can still access Convertpdftoword.org if you setup your browser to not accept cookies. Convertpdftoword.org cookies don't collect personally identifiable information. We only use this information for statistical analysis of visits and to improve the quality of services we offer.

## Security

We apply security practices in order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure. While being fully committed to maintaining a high level of security here at Convertpdftoword.org , please be aware of the fact that there is a level of risk involved in any transmissions of data via the Internet. No transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure.

## Third parties

We will not share, rent, lease or sell any of your data to third parties. We might put advertising links on our website. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. Convertpdftoword.org is not responsible for the advertiser's privacy policy.

## Transfer and sharing of data

In the course of providing the Services data is transferred to and from servers located in the United States. By agreeing to Convertpdftoword.org 's Terms of Service you accept the transfer of such data as is necessary to provide the Services.

## Exceptional Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information only in the case where required by law or if we receive former legal process with respect to a certain document or user of our service.

## Changes in our privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes to this page. This policy was last modified on 06/06/2011.

## Terms and conditions

Please visit our Terms and Conditions section related to the use of this website. [convertpdftoword.org/legal/](http://convertpdftoword.org/legal/)

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please send an email to [online.conversion.service@gmail.com](mailto:online.conversion.service@gmail.com)
